<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<eventList>
  <event>
    <name><![CDATA[Green Festival Expo <br/>
    ]]></name>
    
    <website>
      <![CDATA[
      http://www.going.green/event/green-festival-expo/ <br/>
      ]]>
    </website> 
    <date> 
      <![CDATA[
      April 24, 2015 to April 26, 2015
      ]]>
    </date> 
     
    <description>
        <![CDATA[
      DotGreen Community is one of the sponsors of the upcoming Green Festival to be held in the Javits Center in New York City.  
      The Green Festival is America’s largest and longest running sustainability and green living event. 
      More than 300 exhibitors will be displaying their product, services and “green” information and attendance over the 3 days is expected to be 20,000.<br/>]]> 
      </description>
</event>

  <event>
    <name>
      <![CDATA[Greenbuild 2016 Iconic Green <br/>]]>
    </name>
    <website>
      <![CDATA[http://www.greenbuildexpo.com/
      <br/>
      ]]>
      </website>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[
      October 5, 2015 to October 7, 2015
      <br/>
      ]]>
    </date>
    <description>
        <![CDATA[
      Greenbuild is the premier event for sustainable building.
      Featuring three exhilarating days of uplifting speakers, unmatched networking opportunities, showcases, LEED workshops and tours of green buildings in Washington, DC, Greenbuild offers a place for thousands to gather and renew their commitment to the green movement.
      With so much to see and do, you can't miss the excitement and energy of Greenbuild 2016 in Los Angeles.
    <br/>
      ]]>
    </description>
  </event>

  <event>
    <name>
      <![CDATA[
      21st Conference of the Parties
    <br/>
    ]]>
    
  </name>
    <website>
      <![CDATA[
      http://www.cop21.gouv.fr/en
    <br/>
    ]]>
    </website>
    <date>
      <![CDATA[
      November 30, 2015 to December 11, 2015
      <br/>
      ]]>
    </date>
    <description>
      <![CDATA[
      It will be held in Le Bourget, The French and international civil society gathered to launch the climate Generations areas. 
    Areas dedicated to knowledge, exchange and debate.
    According to the organizing committee, the objective of the 2015 conference is to achieve, for the first time in over 20 years of UN negotiations, a binding and universal agreement on climate, from all the nations of the world.
  <br/>
    ]]>
    </description>
  </event>
</eventList>
